欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
翻译：右翼部鸣明 SG 瓜猫 dieguo 米粒 爷爷
校对：右翼部鸣明 dieguo 依依 牙牙 璇喵
特效/时间轴/压制：开着Bessie的瓦片儿 presisco
史蒂文
♪ Steven ♪
大家都相信着
♪ Everyone believes in ♪
史蒂文
♪ Steven ♪
穿梭于整个宇宙
♪ All across the universe ♪
充满着同情心
♪ Ever compassionate ♪
你能够想象吗？
♪ Can you imagine it? ♪
低谷中与我们同在
♪ Even with us at our worst ♪
钻石的混血儿
♪ Hybrid son of a Diamond ♪
玫瑰的人类之子
♪ Human son of a Rose ♪
这是一个启示 他是革命象征
♪ What a revelation, he's a revolution ♪
爱并成长着的宝石
♪ A Gem that loves and grows ♪
史蒂文
♪ Steven ♪
你听说过他的故事吗？
♪ Have you heard the tale of ♪
史蒂文
♪ Steven? ♪
总是为他人着想
♪ Always putting others first ♪
你能够想象吗？充满着同情心
♪ Can you imagine it? Ever compassionate ♪
史蒂文宇宙
♪ Steven Universe ♪
很久很久以前
Once upon a time,
钻石统治着宝石母星
the Gem Homeworld was ruled by Diamonds --
白钻  黄钻  蓝钻
White, Yellow, Blue,
和最小的钻石  粉钻
and the littlest Diamond, Pink.
其他的钻石征服了
While the other Diamonds conquered
宇宙中的许多星球
many worlds across the galaxy,
粉钻只有一个星球  地球
Pink had only one -- the planet Earth.
一天  粉钻离开了舒适的母星
One day, Pink fled the comforts of Homeworld.
在地球上 建了新家  交了新朋友
On Earth, she made a new home, new friends,
最终  创造了新生命
and finally, new life,
舍弃她的身体来
giving up her form
将自己的宝石遗赠给半人类的儿子
to bequeath her gem to her half-human son.
没了粉钻  宝石人进入了绝望的时代
Without Pink, Gemkind entered an era of despair.
但当史蒂文宇宙了解自己继承的一切后
But when Steven Universe learned of his heritage,
他与其他的钻石重聚
he reunited with his fellow Diamonds
一同开启了和平与自由的新篇章
and championed a new era of peace and freedom
远到不可触及的宇宙中
across the furthest regions of space.
现在  亲爱的宝石们  我很高兴能宣布
And now, dear Gems everywhere, I'm pleased to announce
史蒂文已经准备好归位
that Steven is finally ready to take his rightful place
继承粉钻的王座了
on Pink Diamond's throne.
大家近来还好吗？
How's it going, everybody?
我知道你们都认为我是新的粉钻
I know you all might be thinking of me as the new Pink Diamond,
但你们不用让我坐上王座
but you don't have to put me on a throne.
我有属于自己的位置  就在地球上
I already have a rightful place, and it's on Earth.
-哈？ -什么？
-Huh? -What?
是座海景房  和我朋友们住在一起
It's a beach house, where I live with my friends,
石榴  紫晶和珍珠
Garnet, Amethyst, and Pearl.
虽然我很乐意帮大家废除帝国
As much as I've loved dismantling the Empire
拯救你们的星球
and saving all your planets
我等不及要回家与朋友们一起共度美好时光了
I can't wait to get home and spend some quality time with my friends.
切断直播
Cut the feed.
反正你也没时间了
Your time is up anyway.
我觉得我说得不错
I think that went well.
史蒂文  拜托
Steven, please.
你不能走啊
You can't go.
你必须留下来
You must stay.
粉钻只给我们留下了你
You're all we have left of Pink.
史蒂文 你该和我们一起呆在这里
Steven, you belong here, with us.
呃...  谢谢  不必了
Uh...thanks, but no thanks.
来与我们共住王宫
♪ Come live with us in the palace ♪
这有属于你的房间
♪ There's a room waiting for you ♪
来吧  来吧
♪ Come on ♪ ♪ Come on ♪
来吧
♪ Come on ♪
让我们宠爱你
♪ Just let us adore you ♪
你们在表达爱意上很有进步
You guys have really gotten better at showing affection,
但我有自己的生活
but I've got my own life to get back to.
别忘了  我不是粉钻
Don't forget, I'm not Pink Diamond.
是  我们知道你不是她
♪ Yes, we know that you're not her ♪
但你曾是她
♪ But you were her ♪
你知道爱她是怎样
♪ You know what it meant to love her ♪
而你让我们联想起她
♪ And you remind us so much of her ♪
谢谢了  不过我得走了
Thanks. But I really gotta go.
可史蒂文
But Steven!
我解散了我的军队
I've disbanded my armies.
我解放了我的殖民地
I've liberated my colonies.
我不再打碎其他宝石
I never shatter.
我不再使任何人哭泣
I never make anyone cry.
我会说“请”和“谢谢”
I've been saying "please" and "thank you,"
即使是对低等生物也一样
even to lower life forms.
我之前怎么说的？
What did we talk about?
唉  平等生物
Ugh, equal life forms.
史蒂文  你所要求的所有事我们都做到了
Steven, we've done everything you've asked.
那太棒了  做得好
That's great! Good job.
继续努力  再见
Keep it up. Bye!
史蒂文  怎么花了那么长时间？
Steven! What took so long?
钻石们
The Diamonds.
她们超想我住进去
They really want me to move in.
-为什么？ -因为她们想要时时刻刻用关心淹没我
Why? Because they want to smother me with attention 24/7.
听上去真有趣
Sounds fun.
不  才不呢
No, it doesn't.
我很高兴能在离开前再见你一面
Well, I'm glad I got to see you before heading out.
你真的要去啊？
You're really going through with it?
那当然  我一直想去太空夏令营
Of course. I've always wanted to go to space camp.
可你太空都去了好几次了
But you've literally been to space multiple times.
你所做的事比露营酷得多
And you've done way cooler stuff than just camp there.
我父母尽可能支持我的兴趣
My parents are doing what they can to support my interests.
那真的很好
It's sweet.
而且  我想吃多少冻干冰激凌都可以
Plus, I get all the freeze-dried ice cream I can eat.
可杀手沙蒂和嫌疑犯们今晚有演出
But Sadie Killer and the Suspects are playing tonight.
摇滚演唱会比太空夏令营有趣多了吧？
Isn't a rock show a little better than space camp?
应该与太空夏令营一样有趣
It's maybe equal to space camp.
那是我妈  我该走了
That's my mom. I should get going.
好啦
Okay.
再见
Bye!
告诉夏令营的所有人
Tell everyone at space camp
外太空本来很危险的
that space used to be super scary and dangerous,
但现在都超棒了
but it's great now!
我会的
I will!
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我们来到了未来  一切充满希望
♪ Here we are in the future, and it's bright ♪
没人害怕  没人争斗
♪ Nothing to fear, no one to fight ♪
我无法相信
♪ I can't believe ♪
进步有多大
♪ We've come so far ♪
从此的幸福生活 就在这
♪ Happily ever after, here we are ♪
在很久以前
♪ Once upon a time ♪
我以为我一直会在母亲的影中
♪ I thought I'd always be in my mother's shadow ♪
为她来赎罪
♪ Answering for her crimes ♪
我以为我一直会在不停地战斗
♪ I thought I'd always be in an endless battle ♪
直到我开始练习
♪ Till I began to hone ♪
属于自己的力量
♪ A power all my own ♪
感觉自己每一天  都在成长
♪ That I could feel growing stronger every day ♪
现在我拯救了地球
♪ And now I've saved the world ♪
更是拯救了全宇宙
♪ Not just that, the whole galaxy's saved ♪
我们成功了
♪ We did it ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
嘿 珍珠  嘿 爸爸
Hey, Pearl! Hey, Dad!
嘿  史嘟宝
Hey, Schtuball.
史蒂文  我在练习弹巴斯
Steven! I'm learning to play the "bass."
我一直告诉她  是叫贝斯
I keep tellin' her, it's "base."
不好意思 B-A-S-S拼出来就是巴斯
Excuse me, B-A-S-S spells "bass."
好的老板
You're the boss.
嘿  没错
Heck yes, I am.
在很久以前
♪ Once upon a time ♪
我活着仅仅只为了粉钻服务
♪ I only lived to be of Pink Diamond's service ♪
直到那天我们俩
♪ Till the day the two of us ♪
偷偷地跑来  地球的表面
♪ Snuck down to be on this planet's surface ♪
成就我们的梦想
♪ We became our fantasy ♪
我肯定她赐予我自由
♪ And I was sure she set me free ♪
但最终我并没  离开她身边
♪ But in the end, I guess I never left her side ♪
就在爱与失去与
♪ And after love and loss
所有掉下来的泪  我发现
♪ And all the tears that I cried, I find that ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
嘿  伙计
Hey, buddy.
我到镇上去
I've heading into town.
今晚演唱会见？
See you at the concert tonight?
无论如何都不会错过
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
我们来到了
♪ Here we are ♪
我给你留了个位子
I saved you a seat.
谢了 石榴
Thanks, Garnet.
嘿  伙计们  我错过什么了？
Hey, guys. What'd I miss?
正好讲到我最爱的部分
You're just in time for my favorite part of the story.
在很久以前
♪ Once upon a time ♪
蓝宝来到地球  和她的红宝战士
♪ A Sapphire came to Earth with her Ruby soldier ♪
蓝宝死亡的命运早被决定
♪ Sapphire's deadly fate was set ♪
直到那红宝冲来拯救她
♪ Until the Ruby rushed in to hold her ♪
突然间她们融合了
♪ Suddenly, they were fusing ♪
美妙  奇怪  令人困惑
♪ Beautiful, strange, confusing ♪
成为了我  一个巨大谜团  多幼稚
♪ And there I was, a bundle of questions, so naive ♪
如果你讲述现在的事
♪ That if you told me this ♪
那时的我才不会相信  可现在
♪ I never would have believed you then, but ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
让我把这个存起来
Lemme just save this.
嘿  你知道紫晶在哪里吗？
Hey, any idea what Amethyst is up to?
我知道所有人在哪里
I have every idea what everyone is up to.
你可以在迷你母星找到她
You'll find her if you head to Little Homeworld.
用传送台吧
Take the Warp.
哇哦
Whoa!
小心  伙计
Careful, dude!
砰  砰
Pew! Pew!
一  二  三  嘿
One, two, three, hup!
谢了  紫晶
Thanks, Amethyst.
-哇啊  -史蒂文
-Whoa! -Steven,
来的正是时候
you're just in time!
我们刚准备安装新的传送台
We're about to install the new Warp.
也就是说迷你母星完成度已达到83.7%
Which means Little Homeworld is 83.7% complete.
才83.7%？
Only 83.7%?
我们得加把劲啦
We'd better get cracking.
这就来
I'm on it!
哇  迷你母星成长得真快
Wow. Little Homeworld's growing fast.
你也是啊
So are you.
快看我 我是小年轻
Look at me! I'm a young adult!
我真高兴这些宝石想在地球驻新家
I love that all these Gems want to make their new home on Earth.
真希望我刚成型时也有这样的家
Wish I'd had this when I first emerged.
在很久以前
♪ Once upon a time ♪
我萌发的生命  从幼儿所蹦出
♪ I burst to life inside of the Kindergarten ♪
是战争的产品
♪ A product of a war ♪
却从不知道我为此存在
♪ That I had no idea I had a part in ♪
我姗姗来迟  感到孤独
♪ I came out late and alone ♪
除了这个家  什么也不知道
♪ Knew nothing but my home ♪
但我现在知道
♪ But I know now exactly ♪
我到底是谁
♪ Who I'm s'posed to be ♪
是这大家庭的一成员
♪ And it's a part of this family ♪
你觉得怎样？
So, whaddya think?
如果时间在此刻停止
♪ If I could just stop right here and be ♪
终于结束  终于我们
♪ Finally done, finally us ♪
终于我们
♪ Finally we ♪
来到了未来
♪ Are in the future ♪
我们来到了未来  一切充满希望
♪ Here we are in the future, and it's bright ♪
没人害怕  没人争斗
♪ Nothing to fear, no one to fight ♪
我无法相信  进步有多大
♪ I can't believe we've come so far ♪
从此的幸福生活
♪ Happily ever after ♪
就是现在
♪ Here we are ♪
我希望一切都保持这样的模样
I want everything to stay exactly like this
再也不改变
and never change.
-我赞成  -同意
Agreed. Here, here.
未来看上去如何  石榴？
How's the future look, Garnet?
我们是否永远都保持这样？
Do we all stay just like this forever?
不
No.
嘿 你就是史蒂文宇宙吗？
Hey! Are you Steven Universe?
呃...是的？
Um...yes?
完美
Perfect.
快走
Move!
嘿  停得真不错啊  你这家伙
Hey. Nice park job, dingus.
哎呀呀呀
Well, well, well, well, well.
让我好好瞧瞧你们这群奇珍异兽
Lemme get a look at the menagerie.
你一定是紫晶
You must be Amethyst.
而你就是石榴
You must be Garnet.
还有粉钻的珍珠
And Pink Diamond's Pearl.
哇  她带上了你
Wow. She took you with her.
这可真是...不错
Isn't that just...swell?
这不可能
It can't be.
哦  但这可能
Oh, but it can be,
事实也正是如此
and it is.
我有了个新造型  还有些新玩具
I got a new style and a few new toys
用来终结你们“从此的幸福生活”
that are gonna put an end to your happily ever after
一劳永逸
once and for all!
喔喔  这-这一定是个误会
Whoa, whoa. Th-This has got to be a misunderstanding.
假如你还没听过
In case you haven't heard,
我已经建立了和平的时代  在整个...
I've established peace across the --
是是是  我听说了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I've heard!
我收到了你那条发向宇宙的小消息
I've had your little message to the universe
一直循环播放
on loop!
我真是爱死那部分了
I just love that part
讲的就是粉钻在这颗无名星球上
where Pink Diamond spends the rest of her days
度过她的余生
on this nowhere planet
和一群...无名之辈一起
with a bunch of...nobodies.
没错  这故事我听过  无限循环在耳边
♪ That's right, I heard the story over and over again ♪
嘿 见到她其他的朋友真不赖
♪ Gee, it's swell to finally meet her other friends ♪
没错  这故事我听过
♪ That's right, I heard the story ♪
不大喜欢这结局
♪ Don't really like how it ends ♪
嘿  见到她其他的朋友真不赖
♪ Gee, it's swell to finally meet her other friends ♪
她是怎么说我的？她说了啥？
♪ What did she say about me? What did she say? ♪
没有我你做了什么？ 你在干嘛？
♪ What did you do without me? What did you do? ♪
玩游戏也不带我？ 玩了什么？
♪ Did you play games without me? What did you play? ♪
你觉得这么长时间
♪ Did you think all this time that I wouldn't ♪
我会找不到你？
♪ Find out about you? ♪
哦  没错 这故事我听过  无限循环在耳边
♪ Oh, that's right, I heard the story over and over again ♪
嘿  见到她其他的朋友真不赖
♪ Gee, it's swell to finally meet her other friends ♪
她一直在和我们绕圈子
She's running circles around us.
我已经生疏了 让我歇会儿
I'm rusty. Gimme a break.
真的是她
It really is her.
但她不可能是认真的吧
But she can't be serious.
你认识她  珍珠？
You know her, Pearl?
你能告诉我们她是谁吗？
Can you tell us who she is?
我是谁?我是谁?你到底在说什么？
♪ Who am I? Who am I? What are you even saying? ♪
我是游戏的输家  而你根本不记得参加过
♪ I'm the loser of the game you didn't know you were playing ♪
我们再来一局  这次我一定会赢
♪ Let's play another game, this time, I get to win ♪
命为筹码 赢家通吃
♪ Lives on the line, winner takes all ♪
准备与否  开始吧
♪ Ready or not, let's begin ♪
哦  没错  这故事我听过  无限循环在耳边
♪ Oh, that's right, I heard the story over and over again ♪
嘿  打败她其他的朋友真是棒
♪ Gee, it's swell to finally beat her other friends ♪
哦  没错  这故事我听过
♪ Oh, that's right, I heard the story ♪
不大喜欢这结局
♪ Don't really like how it ends ♪
嘿 打败她其他的朋友  真是
♪ Gee, it's swell to finally beat her other ♪
真是
♪ Other ♪
棒
♪ Friends ♪
够了
That's enough!
啊  怎么了  史蒂文？
Aw, what's the matter, Steven?
已经开始想念你的朋友了？
Miss your friends already?
哦  别担心
Well, don't worry.
下一个就是你
You're right behind 'em!
这点不算什么
That was nothing!
那我猜你不介意我再做一遍
Then I guess you won't mind if I do it again!
别闹了
Cut it out!
你不会被打爆  是吧？
You don't poof, do you?
哼  我早料到了
Hmm. Figured as much.
等着吧
Just wait!
你人类的那一半对抗我的注射器
Your human half won't stand a chance
根本毫无胜算
against my injector.
更别说在我对你的宝石动了手脚之后
Not after what I just did to your gem!
你在说些什么？
What are you talking about?
你并不一直是一个厉害的英雄  不是吗？
You weren't always a powerful hero, were you?
最好在其他意外发生前把你放进泡泡里
Better bubble you before anything else happens.
什么？
What?
我的泡泡去哪了？
Where's my bubble?
拜托
Come on.
发生什么了？
What's going on?
史蒂文  我全速赶来了
Steven! I came as fast as I could!
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
老天...她-她真的打爆了所有人
Holy s-s-she really got everybody!
-这是她？ -是啊
Is that her? Yeah.
-她是？ -不知道
Who -- No idea.
-为什么？ -不知道
Why? No idea.
她怎么做到的？
How?
她用这个攻击了我们每个人
She hit all of us with this.
这还对我造成了奇怪的影响
It did something extra weird to me,
现在我的能力不能正常使用了
and now my powers aren't working right.
看吧
Look.
爸  我感觉我不太对劲
There's something wrong with me, Dad.
但我不清楚发生了什么
I just have no idea what's going on.
哦儿子  现在你理解我大部分时候是什么感受了
Well, son, now you know how I feel almost all the time.
但你还知道吗？
But you know what else?
现在宝石们可能随时
Any moment now, the Gems are gonna do that thing
发光并浮在半空中什么的
where they glow and float in the air
然后以更好的形态重生
and reappear better than ever.
看见没？她来了
See? Here she comes.
我们的老伙计珍珠
Good old Pearl.
这倒挺新鲜的
Well, that's new
请验证你的身份
Please identify yourself.
呃 葛雷格·宇宙？
Um, Greg Universe?
您好 呃葛雷格·宇宙
Greetings, Um Greg Universe.
请设置你的着装偏好选项
Please state preferred customization options.
呃...我现在该说些啥？
Uh... What am I supposed to say here?
我-我不知道
I-I don't know.
已选择默认设置
Default setting selected.
请稍候
Please stand by.
珍珠
Pearl!
珍珠 谢天谢地你回来了
Pearl, thank goodness you're back!
珍珠？
Pearl?
您还好吗？
♪ How do you do? ♪
我的“呃葛雷格·宇宙”先生
♪ My "Um Greg Universe" ♪
感谢您把我带来这世间
♪ Thank you for bringing me into the world ♪
我为您服务 直到永恒
♪ I am at your eternal service ♪
欢迎使用  您的新珍珠
♪ Welcome to your new Pearl ♪
这这这发生了什么？！
Wha-a-at's going on?!
她的宝石是损坏了吗？
Could her gem be cracked?
我觉得没有异常
It looks fine to me.
红宝石  你-你还好吗？
Ruby! Are-Are you okay?
啊  你是谁？
Aah! Who are you?
你不在我的工作范畴里
You're not my assignment.
我真的需要来人解释一下
I could really use an explanation here.
请允许我来阐明
Allow me to illuminate.
红石战士
♪ A Ruby guard ♪
不过只有一个
♪ But just a single one ♪
通常会派遣三个或 更多
♪ They tend to come in teams of three or more ♪
珍贵的蓝宝
♪ A precious Sapphire ♪
能看见未来
♪ She sees the future ♪
她由红宝保护
♪ That's who the Ruby's for ♪
我的蓝宝石
My Sapphire.
以我宣誓之责和唯一目标
As my sworn duty and sole purpose,
我会以生命保护你
I will protect you with my life.
我知道你会  这也是为什么我预言
I know you will. That's why I predict
你撑不过今天
you won't last more than a day.
-嗯?  -来吧
-Huh? -Come, now
紫晶  嘿  紫晶?
Amethyst! Hey -- Amethyst?
嘿  紫晶?
Hey -- Amethyst?
什么?  不 你才是紫晶
What? No. You're Amethyst.
你说对了
♪ You must be right ♪
这的确是紫晶
♪ This is an Amethyst ♪
不过紫晶通常又大又壮
♪ Except an Amethyst is big and strong ♪
这不是最完美的范例
♪ This one is not the best example ♪
显然出现了什么问题
♪ Something is clearly wrong ♪
我说的是  肯定有什么不对劲
I do say, something is clearly wrong.
这些不同的宝石聚在这里做什么？
What are all these different Gems doing here
在这个奇怪的地方？
in this strange place?
珍珠 你难道认不出来他们吗？
Pearl, don't you recognize them?
你难道认不出来我吗？
Don't you recognize me?
哦 我当然认得出我的呃葛雷格·宇宙
Well, I certainly recognize my Um Greg Universe.
哦老天
Oh, boy.
至于你...嗯...
As for you...hmm.
快退后
Get back!
遇到你我好激动
I'm so excited to meet you!
你  你不生气?
Y-You're not mad?
生气? 为什么我要
Mad? Why would I be mad
对我最好的朋友生气
at my best friend!
这真有趣
♪ This will be fun ♪
你真是幸运呀
♪ Aren't you the lucky one? ♪
她切割完美  还是粉红色
♪ Her cut is perfect, and she's pink, as well ♪
能为你带来无限的乐趣
♪ She'll bring you endless entertainment ♪
你的新挚友 尖晶
♪ Your new best friend, Spinel ♪
你
You!!
你对我们做了什么?
What have you done to us?
噗  现在轮到你了
Boop! Now it's your turn!
拜-拜-拜托你停下好吗
W-W-W-Would you cut that out?
求你了
Please?
快看
Hey, look!
这里还有别的宝石
There's more Gems!
问问他们要不要一起玩吧
Let's ask 'em to play.
等-等会儿
W-Wait a minute.
你不记得了吗
You don't remember?
记得什么？
Remember what?
这大家伙真是壮观
That thing sure is big!
你想爬上去吗?
You wanna climb it or somethin'?
等等  你是认真的吗?
Wait, wait. Are you serious right now?
但你刚才还说
What about that stuff you said
我对抗你的注射器根本毫无胜算?
about how I won't stand a chance against your injector?
我刚说了什么?
I said what now?
你真的忘了啊?
You really don't remember, huh?
你呢  狮子?
How 'bout you, Lion?
你能明白这是什么状况吗?
Can you make any sense of this?
算了你也帮不上忙
Aw, you're no help, either.
至少我可以在你的鬃毛里存放这个东西
At least I can store this thing in your mane.
我不能在狮子的鬃毛里放东西了?
I can't store things in Lion's mane now?
这本来是易如反掌的事情呀
That's like the easiest thing I do!
我该怎么办
What do I do?
没有朋友能帮我的忙
I've got no friends to help me,
除了...
except...
铋斯姆  青金石和橄榄石
Bismuth, Lapis, and Peridot.
来吧朋友们  一起想想怎么解决这件事
Come on, guys. Let's go figure out how to fix this.
朋-朋友们?
G-Guys?
我尊敬的呃葛雷格  让我来
My Um Greg, allow me.
红宝石?蓝宝石?
Ruby? Sapphire?
她不会跟你走的
She's not going anywhere with you.
我确实预见到我们跟着去了镇上
I do see us following him to the countryside.
好的我们这就走
Never mind! We're going.
别呀  别留我独自面对这俩货
Wait. Don't leave me alone with these two!
记得留意一下她们
Just keep an eye on them for now.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
她骑着那东西来的?
She rode in on that?!
对  她还说我人类的那一半
Yeah. She said my human half
对抗她的注射器根本毫无胜算
wouldn't stand a chance against her injector.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
为什么我们不直接问她?
Why don't we just ask her?
好吧  是这样的
Well, here's the thing.
她在--
Where'd she -- Aah!
惊喜
Surprise!
介绍一下 我的新挚友  尖晶石
Here she is, my new best friend, Spinel.
很高兴认识你们
A pleasure to meet you all.
我以为你说的是她想杀了你
I thought you said she was just trying to kill you.
-惊天大反转呀这是  -可不是嘛
-Wow. Quick turnaround. -No kidding.
其实我花了好几个月才不再想杀了史蒂文
It took me months to stop trying to kill Steven.
我大概花了一天  还是一天半?
I say it took me a day, day and a half?
我还在戒备状态
I'm still on the fence.
好了 给我们看看她攻击你的武器
Alright, let's see this thing she hit you with.
哦对
Uh, right.
这像是个  射线类的--
Whoa. Was there, like, a laser or --
小心点
Be careful with that.
这是个还原器
It's a rejuvenator.
母星以前常用的武器
Homeworld used to use these things
用在越矩的宝石们身上的
on Gems that started steppin' out of line.
轻轻一击
One hit with this...
你就回到出厂设置了
you're back to how they made you.
你在看什么
What are you lookin' at?
噢我的星啊  我碰到它了
Oh, my stars, I touched it
我苦心经营多年的人设差点崩塌了
I could have lost all my character development.
慢着  你是怎么挨过那个东西的攻击的  史蒂文?
Wait, how did you survive being hit by that thing, Steven?
我-我好像没挨过去
I-I think I didn't.
我的半人体质让我不被打回本体  但--
My human half kept me from poofing, but --
我作为宝石的那一半承受了伤害
but my Gem half, it took the hit.
她把我的能力重置了  仿佛我又变回小孩的时候
She sent me back. It's like I'm a kid again.
我几乎控制不了我的能力了
I can barely control my powers.
我们怎么恢复它?
How do we reverse this?
哦不
Oh, no.
我需要找钻石们帮忙吗?
Do I need to get the Diamonds?
你才是那个拥有治愈能力的人
You're the one with healing powers.
如果有人能恢复的话  那一定是你
If anyone can fix this, it's you.
难以置信
I can't believe this.
多年来的第一次  当大家都身处险境
For the first time in years, everyone's in danger.
所有人都需要我来拯救  而我束手无策
Everybody needs me, and I'm useless.
铋斯姆  我们怎么办?
Bismuth, what do we do?
我很抱歉  史蒂文
I'm sorry, Steven.
我也不知道
I don't know.
石榴肯定知道该怎么办
Garnet would know what to do.
石榴总是知道该怎么办
Garnet always knows what to do.
别自怨自艾了
Hey, don't be sad!
你的新挚友  你的新挚友
♪ Your new best friend, your new best friend ♪
Your new best friend! Your new best friend,
尖晶石  就在这
Spinel, is here!
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我们来到了未来  一切糟糕透顶
♪ Here we are in the future, and it's wrong ♪
就一秒之前  我们还唱着这首歌
♪ Just a second ago, we were singing this song ♪
现在  她们都不在了
♪ And now they're gone ♪
只因为她
♪ Because of her ♪
从此的幸福生活  本就在那
♪ Happily ever after, there we were ♪
人生何时容易过？
♪ When has it ever been easy? ♪
我们一直都在历尽艰苦
♪ Hasn't it always been hard to be us? ♪
当反常的事发生时
♪ When you go against the grain ♪
总有无法信赖的人在身旁
♪ There's always somebody around you can't trust ♪
所以我们必须支持对方
♪ That's why we've got to have each other ♪
我们将一起找到答案
♪ Why, we'll figure this out, we must ♪
因为我们是水晶战士
♪ Because we are the Crystal Gems ♪
我们从不放弃  从不放弃我们的朋友
♪ And we never give up, we never give up on our friends ♪
只要还有一人佩戴着星的标记
♪ As long as one of us is standing to brandish the star ♪
找到办法  拯救世界
♪ We'll find a way to save the day ♪
就是我们
♪ That's who we are ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我们来到了未来  一切糟糕透顶
♪ Here we are in the future, and it's wrong ♪
看看她们  都没有一同歌唱
♪ Look at them, they're not even singing along ♪
如果时间在那时停止
♪ If I coulda just stopped right there, we'd be ♪
完全无事  完整的家  完好的我
♪ Totally fine, totally us, totally me ♪
哪怕要花一千年来拯救她们
♪ Even if it takes a thousand years to get them back ♪
我们也会
♪ We will ♪
她们不知道自己是谁  但我们懂
♪ They may not know who they are, but we do ♪
相信我  史蒂文  我了解她们
♪ Believe me, Steven, I've known them longer ♪
我见过她们经历更糟 变得更强
♪ I've seen them get through worse and come back stronger ♪
所以我相信她们  而我也相信你
♪ That's why I believe in them, and I believe in you ♪
因为我们是水晶战士
♪ Because we are the Crystal Gems ♪
我们从不放弃  不  从不放弃我们的朋友
♪ And we never give up, no, we never give up on our friends ♪
只要还有一个人佩戴着星的标记
♪ As long as one of us is standing to brandish the star ♪
找到办法
♪ We'll find a way ♪
拯救世界
♪ To save the day ♪
就是我们
♪ That's who we are ♪
对  好的
Right. Okay.
让我们一起思考
Let's put our heads together.
一定会有办法找回她们的记忆
There's gotta be some way to make them remember.
如果这就像一个拼图呢
What if it's like a puzzle?
如果把碎片都拼回去
If we give 'em all the pieces,
最终我们就会得到完整的图像了
eventually, they'll get the picture.
尖晶石  你可能说到点子上了
Spinel, you might be onto something.
如果每段回忆就是她们的一片自我碎片
If every experience they lost is a-a piece of who they are,
那我们只要找回这些碎片
we just have to give them back all the pieces,
一次一片
one experience at a time.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
这得找到猴年马月去啊
That could take forever!
正是如此  我们开始吧
Exactly. So, let's get started.
找到办法  拯救世界  就是我们
♪ We'll find a way to save the day, that's who we are ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
Yeah! ♪ Here we are in the future ♪
一切糟糕透顶
♪ And it's wrong ♪
尖晶石  可以了  我们已经唱完了
Whoa, Spinel, it's okay. We're done.
那么  当红宝石和蓝宝石第一次变成石榴时
So, when Ruby and Sapphire first became Garnet,
红宝石冲去救下了蓝宝石
Ruby rushed in to save Sapphire from danger,
然后  磅  她们融合了
and bam -- They fused.
所以也许我们需要制造
So, maybe we've gotta create
一些危险情景
some sort of dangerous situation.
那么  我们手边
Well, what do we have
有什么东西是危险又致命的吗
that's deadly and dangerous laying around?
我想我们可以找找
I think we could dig something up.
危险  危险  危险
Danger, danger, danger.
看我们找到了什么
What have we got?
嗯…不行
Hmm. No.
啊哈
Aha!
一把巨大的披萨刀?
A giant pizza cutter?
是 这只是它的功能之一
That is one of its functions, yes.
我没法用这个威胁她们
I can't threaten them with this.
嗯…好了
Hmm. Here.
现在比较有威胁了
Now it's much more threatening.
现在快去吧
Off you go, now.
祝你好运
Good luck!
嗯? 站住
Hmm? Halt!
我不能让你拿着
I cannot allow you to approach my Sapphire
如此危险的设备靠近我的蓝宝石
with such a threatening device.
那太糟糕了  因为我要……攻击你们
That's too bad, 'cause I'm gonna...get you!
能成功吗
Will this work?
请允许我处决这个卷毛  我的蓝宝石
Permission to dispatch the curly-haired one, my Sapphire?
不必了  我预测到他不会继续动手
No need. I predict he won't be able to follow through.
她说的没错
She's right.
我做不到
Ugh, I can't.
即使我们只是假装的
Even if we are just pretending.
我的蓝宝石  你说得对
My Sapphire, you were right!
你还能预测到接下来会发生什么吗
What do you predict will happen next?
尖晶石会出于好奇捡起那件设备
Well, the Spinel will pick up that device out of curiosity.
接着骚乱会发生
Hijinks will ensue.
也许我们可以试试…
Maybe we should try --
等等  尖晶石  别别别别
Wait, Spinel. No, no, no, no!
别碰那玩意
Don't touch that thing!
嘿  我们刚建起来的呢
Hey, we just built that!
她往这边来了
Whoa, here she comes!
尖晶石
Spinel!
我的脚手架
My scaffolding.
我的宝贝脚手架啊
My precious scaffolding!
哇  接下来呢
Wow! What happens next?
眨眼之间
In just a moment,
那些脚手架会掉落到你周围
the scaffolding will start falling all around you.
什么
What?
哇  你太厉害了
Wow. You're amazing!
接下来  橄榄石会稳住
Hmph. Next, the Peridot will hold back
一些摇摇欲坠的碎片
some of the falling debris.
三个大桶会掉下来
Three large barrels will fall.
铋斯姆会接住其中两个
The Bismuth will catch two of them.
这个我来 铋斯
I got this, Biz!
干得好  橄榄--糟糕
Nice work, Perido-- Oh, shucks!
啊 惨了
Ah. Shoot!
哦不!  天地甲壳虫
Oh, no! The Heaven and Earth Beetles
正在享受她们的午后健身呢
are out for their afternoon constitutional!
青金石会冲下来 在最后关头救走她们
The Lapis will rush in and save them at the last second.
好险 你们没事吧
Whew. You guys okay?
哇哦  结束…了?
Whoa. Is it...over?
锯齿
The saw.
锯齿刀不会停下
The saw will continue to cut.
然后铁砧就会砸下来
The anvil will fall.
而你--你会被粉碎
And you -- you will be shattered.
卷毛的力量正在衰退
The curly-haired one's power is fading.
红宝石 对不起!
Ruby, I'm sorry!
我早说过 你撑不过今天
I told you you wouldn't last the day.
那 我还是很高兴 命运让我遇见你
Well, I'm glad fate allowed me to meet you.
不!
No!
突然炽热 我变得
♪ Suddenly hot, I'm ♪ ♪ Ooh ♪
突然冷澈 我变得
♪ Suddenly cool, I'm ♪ ♪ Ooh ♪
一时聪敏 一时愚钝 我怎么
♪ Suddenly a genius, I'm suddenly a fool, I'm ♪
突然真实 但我感觉
♪ Ooh ♪ ♪ Suddenly fact, but I feel ♪
比虚构更加奇异  全新的我
♪ Stranger than fiction, I'm new ♪
突然回归自我  我是行走的悖论
♪ But I'm suddenly back, I'm a walking contradiction ♪
这种感觉不可名状
♪ Doesn't this have a name? ♪
这般体验不可名状
这份感情不可名状
♪ Doesn't this have a name? ♪
这是不是  是不是
♪ And isn't it, isn't it ♪
被称作爱？
♪ Isn't it love? ♪
这是不是  是不是  被称作爱？
♪ Isn't it, isn't it, isn't it love? ♪
♪ And isn't it, isn't it, isn't it love? ♪
这是不是  是不是  被称作爱？
♪ Isn't it, isn't it, isn't it love? ♪
石榴!
Garnet!
石榴  你回来了!
Garnet! You're back!
谢天谢地  真的是你
Thanks goodness it's you.
这-这是怎么回事?
W-W-What's going on?
大家的记忆都被抹去了  我的力量陷入了混乱
Everyone's memories are wiped, and my powers are all messed up.
我们需要你帮忙!
We need your help!
接下来该怎么办  石榴?
What should we do, Garnet?
抱歉  可是…
I'm sorry, but...
你认识我吗?
do you know me?
好问题
Good question.
她的记忆并没有恢复
Her memories aren't back.
我猜融合只是第一步
I guess fusion was only the first piece.
大家注意了
Attention, everyone.
尊贵的呃葛雷格·宇宙  驾到
Um Greg Universe has arrived.
史蒂文!
Steven! Oh!
你看见紫晶了吗?
Have you seen Amethyst?
啥? 我让你看好她
What? I told you to watch her.
她肯定是在我拼命
She must have wandered off
从珍珠手里抢衣服的时候溜走了
while I was wrestling my laundry out of Pearl's hands.
珍珠!你根本不用擦轮胎
Pearl! You don't have to do that.
我是开洗车店的!
I own a car wash!
我要去找紫晶
I need to go find Amethyst.
你能照顾下石榴吗?  当然
Can you watch Garnet? Yeah, sure.
不过看起来她照顾起自己来
But it looks like she's doing a pretty good job
正得心应手
watching herself.
谢了
Thanks.
别忘了你的好朋友 尖晶石!
Don't forget your best friend, Spinel!
噢 好吧
Oh, right.
尖晶石  你和大家一起留下
Spinel, you stay here with the others,
我去去就回
and I'll be right back.
不行!
No!
好-好吧
O-Okay.
我们一起去?
Let's go together?
好耶!
Yay!
紫晶?
Amethyst?
紫晶! 你在哪?
Aah! Amethyst?
紫晶?
Amethyst?
等下 我能打包一点儿吗?
Wait, can I get a couple to go?
紫晶!
Amethyst!
我这有好吃的甜甜圈哦!
I've got tasty donuts!
快过来拿呀!
Come and get 'em!
值得一试
Worth a try.
她能去哪儿呢?
Where can she be?
紫晶?
Amethyst?
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
这是间艺术工作室
I-It's an art studio.
紫晶过去常到这里来
Amethyst used to come here all the time.
紫晶  谢天谢地你没事
Amethyst, thank goodness you're okay.
谢天谢地你没事
Thank goodness you're okay.
我有事
I'm very not okay,
不过我有个计划
but I've got a plan.
我会一片一片把你遗失的回忆拼起来
I'm gonna get us all back piece by piece.
只要知道你遗失的是哪些片段
I just have to figure out your pieces.
这些画
These paintings.
你还记得被画下来的时候吗
Do you remember being painted?
被画下来?
Being painted?
砰  砰! 你还记得我们的握手吗?
Pew, pew! Do you remember our handshake?
我们的握手?
Our handshake?
唱歌和跳舞  回忆里肯定有这个片段
Singing and dancing, that's gotta be a piece.
你记得和我一起又唱又跳吗?
Do you remember singing and dancing with me?
在耀眼日光之下  在深夜黑暗之中
♪ In the light of the day, in the dark of the night ♪
当你士气高涨
♪ When you're rarin' to go ♪
当你筋疲力竭
♪ When you're tired from the fight ♪
当你丧失理智  让我来告诉你
♪ When you're losing your mind, lemme give you a thought ♪
无论如何我都会呆在你身旁
♪ I'm gonna be right by your side, no matter what ♪
在深夜黑暗之中
♪ In the dark of the night ♪
在耀眼日光之下
♪ In the light of the day ♪
当你朝气蓬勃
♪ When you're risin' to shine ♪
当你酣然入眠
♪ When you're hittin' the hay ♪
我会在你身旁
♪ I'll be hangin' around ♪
无论你喜欢与否
♪ If you like it or not ♪
我都会
♪ I'm gonna be ♪
呆在你身旁  无论如何
♪ Right by your side, no matter what ♪
-无论如何 -无论如何
♪ No matter what ♪ ♪ No matter what ♪
哦    我都会呆在
♪ Oh, I'm gonna be ♪
呆在你身旁  我会
♪ Right by your side ♪ ♪ I'm gonna ♪
呆在你身旁  无论如何
♪ Be right by your side no matter what ♪
在深夜黑暗之中  在耀眼日光之下
♪ In the dark of the night, in the light of the day ♪
当你朝气蓬勃  当你酣然入眠
♪ When you're risin' to shine, when you're hittin' the hay ♪
只要记住这首歌
♪ Just remember this song ♪
怎么唱的？我忘了
♪ How's it go? I forgot ♪
我会
♪ I'm gonna be ♪
呆在你身旁  无论如何
♪ Right by your side no matter what ♪
所有你的经历
♪ Through whoever you've been ♪
所有你的未来
♪ Through whoever you'll be ♪
所有你失去的
♪ Through whatever you lose ♪
你都能依靠我
♪ You will always have me ♪
当你束手无策
♪ At the end of your rope ♪
我会助你一臂
♪ I'll be holdin' you taught ♪
我会呆在你身旁
♪ I'm gonna ♪ ♪ Be right by your side ♪
无论如何
♪ No matter what ♪
呆在你身旁  呆在你身旁
♪ Be right by your side, be right by your side ♪
呆在你身旁  无论如何
♪ Be right by your side no matter what ♪
砰!
Pew!
砰  砰?
Pew, pew?
一 二 三 嘿
One, two, three, hup.
紫晶!
Amethyst!
哦哦  发生了什么?
Ohh, what happened?
成功了! 你回来了 紫晶!
Amethyst, it worked! You're back!
是你! 怎么--
You! Wha--
你-你在这里干嘛?
W-What are you doing here?!
我可以解释
So, l-let me explain.
离他远一点  你这个怪物!
Get away from him, you monster!
怪物?
A monster?
在哪里?
Where is it?
我怎么没看见
No, I don't see it.
啊 你就是
Aah. You're it.
准备好了吗  我来啦!
Ready or not, here I come!
噗!
Boop!
啊! 我忘记说"你就是鬼"了!
Oh! I forgot to say "you're it"!
好吧 砰 你就是鬼!
Okay, tag, you're it!
她到底在搞什么鬼?
What the heck is this about?
她不记得攻击我们的事了
She doesn't remember attacking us.
她连那个也不记得了
She doesn't even remember that thing.
什么鬼…
What the...
呃 你们是不知道怎么玩抓鬼游戏吗?
Mm, you guys not know how to play tag?
史蒂文 这到底是怎么回事?
Steven, what is going on here?
我也不清楚 但我会弄明白的
I'm not sure, but I'll find out.
快打开避难所  我们或许需要疏散
Let's open up the shelters. We might need to evacuate.
青金石  铋斯姆  橄榄石!
Lapis, Bismuth, Peridot!
现在情况怎样?
What's the damage?
紫晶  离我远点
Amethyst, get away from me.
我受不了看你
I can't stand to see you all vacant
失落空虚的样子
and bereft of personality.
唷  我可回来了  你才走开
Yo, I'm back, you dip.
哦  那好啊  回来正赶上世界末日
Oh! Well, you're just in time for the end of the world!
这不是一般的注射器
This is no ordinary injector.
它渗透往地下的液体有毒
Whatever it's leaking into the ground is toxic.
看看我们要对付的东西扫描出来是什么结果
Let's get a scan going and see what we're dealing with.
不出我所料
Just as I thought.
生物毒素  高纯度无稀释
Bio-poison. Pure and uncut.
现在来说  针管已经打入了
As of this moment, the ampoule has drained
占总量15.4%的液体  也就是说毒素正以
15.4% of its contents, meaning the poison is releasing
每小时5立方米的破坏速率释放着
at a destruction rate of 5 cubic meters per hour,
我们只剩下  嗯…
giving us, hmm...
41小时  到那时  地球上所有的有机生命都会死亡
41 hours until the destruction of all organic life on Earth.
所有有机生命?
All organic life?
对啊  比如动物  植物  昆虫
Yeah, like the animals, the plants, the insects.
你懂的  还有人类
You know...people.
噢  不
Oh, no.
原来尖晶石是这个意思
This is what Spinel meant.
“你人类的那一半对抗我的注射器根本毫无胜算”
"Your human half won't stand a chance against my injector."
她…她是要用这东西杀了我
She -- She brought this thing here to kill me,
而现在 -- 还要连着地球上所有生命一起杀?
and now -- now it's gonna kill everything else on Earth, too?
我必须做点什么
I've got to do something!
-不行  史蒂文  等等  -史蒂文  快停下
No, Steven, wait! Steven! Stop!
超级史蒂文能量
Super Steven strength!
史蒂文  小心
Steven! Careful!
那个野蛮人在想什么呢
What is that clod thinking?
就是这样  用腿使劲
Yeah! Lift with your legs!
哦  看我钓上了什么
Well, look what I reeled in.
史蒂文  你没事吧
Steven! Are you okay?
我的有机夹克破了
My organic jacket.
我现在这个样子使用不了我的治愈能力
I can't do anything with my powers like this.
铋斯姆  青金石  你们不能把那东西举起来吗
Bismuth, Lapis, can't you lift that thing?
橄榄石  你的金属控制能力呢
Peridot, what about your metal powers?
你认为我们没有尝试吗
You think we didn't try that?
干扰注射器
Disturbing the injector
会加速毒药的扩散速度
accelerates the poison's rate of release.
另外  它也有可能爆炸
Also, it might explode.
我们得想办法在不直接触碰的前提下移动它
We have to find a way to move it without touching it,
趁现在还来得及
before it's too late.
尖晶石-- 是她激活的
Spinel --She activated it,
她也一定可以关闭它
so she must be able to deactivate it,
但她甚至不记得这是什么东西了
but she doesn't even remember what it is,
更别说怎么操作了
let alone how to control it.
那你就得把她变回来
Then you gotta change her back.
绝对不行
No way!
她现在是看起来可爱又无害
She's cute and harmless now,
但如果我们把她变回来  她会把我们团灭的
but if we bring her back, she'll kill us all!
要是你不让她把那东西关掉
You're going to die anyway
你还是要玩完
if you don't get her to deactivate that thing.
她说的对  史蒂文  你之前把我变回来了
She's right, Steven. You got me back.
就用你对我的方法把她也变回来好了
Whatever you did for me, just do it for her.
这不一样  我了解你
That's different. I know you.
但我一点都不了解尖晶石
I don't know anything about Spinel.
我们之前没人听说过她
hNone of us had ever even heard of her before.
除了…珍珠
Except...Pearl.
珍珠认识她
Pearl knew her.
恐怕我帮不上忙
I'm afraid I can't help.
我最近正忙于服务我的呃葛雷格·宇宙
I'm currently in the service of my Um Greg Universe,
准备今晚的演唱会
preparing for tonight's concert,
展示一个非常有希望的
showcasing a promising ensemble
摇滚体裁的合奏组
in the "rockinroll" genre.
你要把人疏散到仓库?
You're evacuating people to the warehouse?
我--我会取消摇滚表演
I'll -- I'll cancel the rock show.
不？你是对的
No? You're right.
杀手莎蒂总能吸引大批人群
Sadie Killer always draws a crowd.
没问题  市长  门票免收
You got it, Mayor. I'll drop the cover charge
以及  见鬼  周边都打七折
and, heck, 30% off merch.
-爸  -史蒂文  你找到紫晶了
Dad. Steven, you found Amethyst!
紫晶是谁
Who is Amethyst?
哦不  她变得更糟了
Oh, no. She's even worse.
才没有  只是开玩笑啦
Nah, I'm just goofin'.
太早了吧  紫晶
Too soon, Amethyst.
石榴  你没事吧
Garnet, are you okay?
你想要这根红线还是这根蓝线
Did you want the red cable or the blue cable?
这无关紧要  它们都是一样的
It doesn't matter! They're the same!
珍珠  你在干什么呢? 那些东西我们表演要用啊
Pearl, what are you doing? We need those for the show!
谁还管什么摇滚表演
Who cares about the rock show?
我们要去关闭尖晶石的注射器
We have to stop Spinel's injector,
不然地球上的所有人都会死
or everyone on Earth is going to die!
要关闭注射器  我们需要把尖晶石变回来
To stop it, we need Spinel back,
要做到这一点  我们需要把珍珠变回来
and to do that, we need Pearl back,
然后要做到这个  我们要找回她缺失的记忆碎片
and to do that, we need her missing pieces.
珍珠和我妈共同反抗了母星  所以她要和你一起反抗才行
Pearl and Mom rebelled together, so she's gotta rebel with you.
我们需要筹划一些盛大的  戏剧性的事件
We've gotta stage some big, dramatic event,
来唤醒她的记忆  比如-- 比如--
something to jog her memory, like -- like --
一场摇滚表演
Like a rock show!
一场摇滚表演?
Like a rock show?
没错
Yes!
这边走  市民们
Right this way, citizens.
是来看表演的还是被疏散的?
Ticker holder or evacuee?
谁是来看表演的?
Who's here for the show?!
谁是因为世界末日而来的?
Who's here 'cause it's the end of the world?!
等等  啥
Wait, what?
第一首歌来自史蒂文宇宙的特别要求
This first song's a special request from Steven Universe!
这肯定可以唤起珍珠的回忆
This has gotta bring Pearl's memories back.
它就是有关辞掉一份糟糕的服务工作的
It's all about quitting a crummy service job.
谢谢  谢谢  谢谢大家
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
承蒙各位赏光
Thank you for gracing me with your presence.
下午好 先生  有什么我能为您做的  先生
♪ Good afternoon, sir, what can I do, sir? ♪
请说出您的要求  先生  任何事都可以  先生
♪ Just say the word, sir, anything for you, sir ♪
你的朋友们都说  先生  “你配不上她”
♪ Your friends all say, sir, "You don't deserve her" ♪
我不同意  先生  我生来为您服务  先生
♪ I disagree, sir, I live to serve, sir ♪
我想起那些我浪费的时光
♪ I think about all the wasted time I spent ♪
我想要反抗
♪ I wanna be disobedient ♪
梦中惊醒彷徨  我的夏天去了何方
♪ I shoot awake wondering where my summers went ♪
我想要反抗
♪ I wanna be disobedient ♪
反抗  反抗
♪ Disobedient, disobedient ♪
我一直做的很好  先生  非常非常好  但为了什么
♪ I've been good, sir, so very, very good, for what? ♪
而我已经献上我的一切
♪ And I've given you every single thing I've got ♪
整个安排  天哪  都令人迷茫
♪ It's feeling strange, man, this whole arrangement ♪
最终让我彻底疯狂
♪ Is gonna end with me totally deranged ♪
我想起那些我浪费的时光
♪ When I think about all the wasted time I spent ♪
我想要反抗
♪ I wanna be disobedient ♪
梦中惊醒彷徨  我的夏天去了何方
♪ I shoot awake wondering where my summers went ♪
我想要反抗
♪ I wanna be disobedient ♪
反抗  反抗
♪ Disobedient, disobedient ♪
稍等
One sec.
这还不够
I-It's not enough.
也许我们要唤醒她的心理创伤
Maybe we need to hit her where it hurts.
-什么?  -你懂的  她原本的主人
What?You know, her original boss?
她的毕生挚爱?
The love of her life?
她最初反抗母星的理由
The reason she rebelled in the first place.
妈妈  她必须想起我妈妈
Mom. She's gotta remember Mom.
-但是…  -如果必要的话 那就做吧
But -- If that's what it takes.
我想要
♪ I want to be ♪
反抗
♪ Disobedient ♪
我想要
♪ I want to be ♪
反抗  反抗
♪ Disobedient, disobedient ♪
这怎么可能没用呢?
How could that not work?
我们忽略了什么吗?
What are we missing?
不用担心  我可以替你鼓掌
Don't worry! I can clap for you!
啊  到底怎样才可以让你停止服务我
Ah! What will make you stop serving me?
只要你还存在  我就会一直服务您
As long as you exist, I will serve you.
“只要你还存在”
"As long as you exist."
这就是我们最后缺少的碎片
That's the final piece.
妈妈消失了
Mom disappeared.
爸  我有个想法
Dad, I've got an idea.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你不是无法正常使用能力吗
Aren't your powers messed up?
至少我可以试试
I can at least try.
那我呢? 我还从来没有--
But what about me? I've never --
来吧  爸  让我们一起二重唱
Come on, Dad. Let's duet.
拜托了  能力  配合我一下吧
Come on, powers, work with me here.
呃葛雷格
Um Greg?
史蒂文
Steven?
宇宙  宏大又古老
It's a big, old universe out there.
当你感觉自己要被那些星辰的重量压碎
And when you're gettin' crushed under the weight of them stars...
什么-- 在哪--
Wha-- Where --
有时候  你需要一位特别的人
Well, sometimes, you need that special someone
来提醒你的潜力不止于此
to remind you that you're so much more.
啥…
Wha...
没有什么
♪ Nothing ♪
可以让你停滞不前
♪ Is holding you back now ♪
再没有人
♪ No one ♪
可以将你任意摆布
♪ Can push you around ♪
你想做什么?
♪ What do you wanna do? ♪
你的人生由你主宰
♪ You're the master of you ♪
难道此念不足以让你升举上天
♪ And isn't the thought enough to lift you off'a the ground? ♪
没有什么
♪ Nothing ♪
可以让我停滞不前
♪ Is holding me back now ♪
再没有人
♪ No one ♪
可以将我随意摆布
♪ Can push me around ♪
我想做什么
♪ What do I wanna be? ♪
我的人生由我主宰
♪ I'm the master of me ♪
难道此念不足以将我
♪ And isn't the thought enough to lift me ♪
升举上天
♪ Off'a the ground? ♪
我们可以一起独立
♪ We could be independent together ♪
一起独立  自由飞翔
♪ Independent together, we can fly ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
一起独立  你我携手
♪ Independent together, you and I ♪
无边海洋的九天之上
♪ High above an endless sea ♪
除我无人将我们携至此方
♪ No one brought us here but me ♪
每一脚步  每一抉择
♪ Every step and every choice ♪
是我的责任  是我的想法  是我的话语
♪ It's my fault, it's my thought, it's my words ♪
是我的声音
♪ It's my voice ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
一起独立  若我们尝试
♪ Independent together, if we try ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
一起独立  你我携手
♪ Independent together, you and I ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
一起独立  自由飞翔
♪ Independent together,we can fly ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
一起独立  你我携手
♪ Independent together, you and I ♪
一起独立
♪ Independent together ♪
你我携手
♪ You and I ♪
你成功了  史蒂文？
You did it! Steven?
等等
Wait.
尖晶石
Spinel!
史蒂文 你还好吧？
Steven, are you okay?
不用担心我  现在重点是尖晶石
D-Don't worry about me. It's Spinel.
我们需要让她回想起怎么关闭她的注射器
We need her to remember how to stop her injector.
呃  珍珠  你知道她的过去吗?
Ugh! Pearl, what do you know about her?
尖晶石?她以前是粉钻的小玩伴
Spinel? She was Pink Diamond's little playmate.
她们曾经年年在粉钻的花园里共同玩耍
They used to spend ages together in Pink's garden --
-花园?  -就是她们以前玩的地方
-Garden? -That's where they used to play.
所以呢  她跟我们有什么关系?
So, what's her problem with us?
我不知道  我已经六千年没见过她了
I don't know. I haven't seen her in 6,000 years.
这期间肯定发生了什么
Something must have happened to her since then.
那么我们就去找出来是什么
Then that's what I need to find out.
哇  小子  你确定不要歇一歇？
Whoa, kiddo, are you sure you don't need a break?
融合看起来把你的力气用光了
It looks like that fusion took everything out of you.
我必须不遗余力地去做能做的事
I've gotta do what I can with the little I have left.
我去追尖晶石
I'm going after Spinel.
史蒂文  等等
Steven, wait!
史蒂文  有些人掉队了  没进避难所
Oh, Steven, some stragglers are missing from the shelters!
你有没有见到一个粉色的宝石人？
Did you see a pink Gem run by?
谢谢
Thanks.
早上的时候一切还是那么完美
Just this morning, everything was perfect.
为什么一切都会变？
Why did everything have to change?
还我从此的幸福生活
I want my happily ever after back.
那大概就是她了
That might be her.
去找康妮  我们需要集中人手
Go find Connie. We need all hands on deck.
尖晶石
Spinel?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我只是开始感受到一些感情汹涌而至
I just started getting these feelings flooding back to me.
那-那很好啊
That's -- That's good.
我需要你想起来
I need you to remember.
否则  我和我的家园就要完了
If you don't, something really bad will happen to me and my home.
快想起来吧
Please, think!
你记得那个花园吗？
Do you remember the garden?
花园？
The garden?
你有回想起什么吗？
Is anything coming back to you?
不
No!
尖晶石  我们要去哪？
Spinel, where are we going?
回到...我从未离开过的地方
Back... to where I never left.
尖晶石
Spinel!
这是我们以前的花园
This was our garden.
一个特别的世界
A special world,
只为我和粉钻而造
built just for Pink and I.
在母星时  粉钻孤单而难过
On Homeworld, Pink was so lonely and sad,
但在这里不同
but not here.
在这里  我们一玩就是好几个小时
Here, we would play for hours.
每一天都曾那么有趣
Every day was so much fun.
至少...我以前是这么想的
At least... that's what I thought.
发生了什么？
Did something happen?
粉钻最大的愿望是拥有一个殖民地
Pink wanted a colony more than anything.
有一天  她的心愿成真了
One day, her wish came true!
蓝钻和黄钻给了粉钻一个她专属的星球——
Blue and Yellow gave Pink her very own planet --
地球
Earth!
我那时非常激动
I was so excited!
那是一个全新的乐园
A brand-new place to play.
那你为什么没跟着她？
So, why didn't you go with her?
在这花园里  来玩游戏
♪ Here in the garden let's play a game ♪
我来教你怎么玩
♪ I'll show you how it's done ♪
在这花园里  站着别动
♪ Here in the garden stand very still ♪
这一定很有趣
♪ This'll be so much fun ♪
然后她笑了  我就盼着她
♪ And then she smiled, that's what I'm after ♪
眼中的笑意  欢笑的声音
♪ The smile in her eyes, the sound of her laughter ♪
高兴地听从  高兴地玩
♪ Happy to listen, happy to play ♪
高兴地看着她  飘散不见
♪ Happily watching her drift away ♪
高兴地等待  独自一人
♪ Happily waiting all on my own ♪
无尽的天空下
♪ Under the endless sky ♪
数着过去的  每分每秒
♪ Counting the seconds standing alone ♪
千年的时间消逝
♪ As thousands of years go by ♪
高兴地猜想  每日每夜
♪ Happily wondering night after night ♪
是这样玩吗？我没搞错吧？
♪ Is this how it works? Am I doing it right? ♪
高兴地听从  高兴地留下
♪ Happy to listen, happy to stay ♪
高兴地看着她  飘散不见
♪ Happily watching her drift away ♪
你总在翻动扉页
♪ You keep on turning pages ♪
为不在乎的人
♪ For people who don't care ♪
不在乎你的那人
♪ People who don't care about you ♪
可依旧 花费多年
♪ And still, it takes you ages ♪
才发现没人回来  没人回来
♪ To see that no one's there, see that no one's there ♪
没有人回来  大家都已离开
♪ See that no one's there, everyone's gone on ♪
只剩你
♪ Without you ♪
终于有了消息  等来了新闻
♪ Finally something, finally news ♪
故事的结局如何
♪ About how the story ends ♪
她早不存在了  只剩她的儿子
♪ She doesn't exist now, survived by her son ♪
和她的新朋友们
♪ And all of her brand-new friends ♪
难道那不愉快吗? 难道那不棒吗?
♪ Isn't that lovely? Isn't that cool? ♪
难道那不残忍吗? 难道我不是傻瓜吗?
♪ And isn't that cruel? And aren't I a fool ♪
高兴地听从  高兴地留下
♪ To have happily listened, happy to stay ♪
高兴地看着她
♪ Happily watching her drift ♪
飘散
♪ Drift ♪
飘散不见
♪ Away? ♪
尖-尖晶石  你-你找回记忆了
S-Spinel, you-you've got your memories back.
我不敢相信妈妈对你做了这种事
I can't believe Mom did that to you.
事实上  我完全相信
Actually, I can totally believe it.
她伤害过的人不止是你
You're not the only one she hurt.
对 除了我的事 你对她的人生了如指掌
Yeah, you must know all about her life without me!
伤口撒盐啊  继续啊
Rub it in, why don't ya?!
不  不是那样的
No! It's not like that!
你值得更好的朋友
You deserve a better friend.
尖晶石  和我回去拯救地球吧
Spinel, come back and save the Earth with me.
你可以在那里重新开始 交上新朋友
You can start over there, make new friends.
某天  某处  以某种办法
♪ Someday, somewhere, somehow ♪
你能再爱
♪ You'll love again ♪
你只需找到某人
♪ You just need to find someone ♪
某天  某处  以某种办法
♪ Someday, somewhere, somehow ♪
-你能再爱  -我能再爱
♪ You'll love again ♪ ♪ I'll love again ♪
-你只需找到 -我只需找到
♪ You just need to find ♪ ♪ I just need to find ♪
某人
♪ Someone ♪
-对你更好的  -对我更好的
♪ Who treats you better ♪ ♪ Who treats me better ♪
-想以你为伴的某人  -想以我为伴的某人
♪ Someone who wants you around ♪ ♪ Someone who wants me around ♪
某天  某处  某种办法
♪ Someday, somewhere, somehow ♪
不再感到迷失
♪ You're gonna feel found ♪ ♪ I'm gonna feel found ♪
今天  此时  此刻
♪ Today, right here, right now ♪
我已经不再迷失
♪ I already feel found ♪
要是他找到她了  他就会回这里  对吧？
If he finds her, he'll come back here, right?
大伙儿  猜猜谁回来了？
Guys! Guess who's back?
下来吧
Come on down.
看到我这个样子她们不会歇斯底里吗？
Won't they all be not exactly incredibly thrilled to see me like this?
我们只需要和她们谈一谈
We just have to talk to them.
什什什什什么？！
W-W-W-W-What?!
哦  尖晶石  你换发型了？
Oh, Spinel, did you change your hair?
尖晶石找回记忆了  但是她不会伤害大家了
Spinel got her memories back, but she's not gonna hurt us.
大家都和和气气
Everything's chill.
哈   我来了  哪里要开打？！
Hah! I'm here! Where's the fight?!
不要打架  和和气气
Don't fight! Everything's chill!
啊  行吧行吧
Aah. Alright, alright.
我去洗手
I'll wash my hands.
呼  好了
Whew. Okay.
尖晶石  你能帮我个忙吗？
Spinel, can I ask you a favor?
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?
什么忙都没问题
Anything.
听起来很糟
That sounds bad.
看起来很糟
That looks bad.
的确是很糟
That is bad.
我们正在达到临界点
We're hitting critical mass.
那我猜我们及时赶到了
Then I guess we're just in time.
史蒂文  尖晶石现在是什么状态?
Steven! What's the status on Spinel?
她找回了自我  现在她回来帮忙了
She's back, and she's here to help.
好吧  有谁可以给我前情提要一下?
Okay, can someone fill me in?
谢谢 尖晶石
Thanks, Spinel.
哦  天
Aw, gee.
朋友就是这样嘛
What are friends for?
好了  我们马上就能收拾好这个烂摊子了
Okay, we've almost cleaned up this mess.
现在我们只需要把石榴的记忆和我的能力找回来
Now all we need are Garnet's memories and my powers,
然后我们就能回到幸福美满的结局了
and we can all get back to living happily ever after.
石榴的记忆应该怎么找呢
What could work for Garnet?
一些关于融合  关于爱的事…
Something about fusion, something about love...
那我呢
What about me?
这就是你找我唯一的目的吗?
Is that all you needed me for?
就为了关掉我的注射器?
To turn off my injector?
不 这个…也有部分原因是  但…
No. Well... sort of, but --
那么现在呢? 我已经按你的要求做了
Well, what now? I-I did what you wanted.
-然后就没有然后了?  -呃  是啊
-That's it? -Well, yeah.
我们可以…就当做这件事没有发生过
We can just...forget this whole thing ever happened.
有我在你怎么能当做无事发生?
How you gonna forget with me around?
我是你所有麻烦的源头
I'm the source of all your problems.
别装的好像你希望我待在这里
Don't pretend you want me here.
你打算怎么处置我  嗯? 你想把我放置在哪?
What's your plan for me, huh? You gonna put me somewhere?
你想把我丢在哪儿? 你想把我一个人丢下?
You gonna leave me somewhere? You gonna leave me alone?
尖晶石
Spinel.
噢  这是什么
Oh, what's this?
石榴  别  别碰
G-Garnet, d-don't touch that!
你怎么会有那个?
Why do you have that?
我  我只是暂时保管
I-I was just carrying it.
我  我没有地方可以放它
I-I didn't have anywhere else to put it.
“我们可以就当做这件事没有发生过"
We can just forget this ever happened."
你是指我可以忘记这件事发生过
You mean I can just forget this ever happened!
真是个绝妙的计划
What a plan!
我关掉注射器
I turn off the injector,
然后等我一转身
and then the moment my back is turned --
嗙  变  记忆消除  问题解决
Bam! Presto! Change-o! Problem solved!
再好好想想吧
Well, think again.
你可休想轻易摆脱我
You're not getting rid of me that easy.
快跑
Run for it!
我不会让你得逞的  史蒂文·宇宙
I'm not letting you get one over on me, Steven Universe.
我没打算消除你的记忆  尖晶石
I wasn't going to wipe your memories, Spinel.
你要怎么让我相信  你想要我现在这个样子
You expect me to believe that you want me like this?
史蒂文?
Steven?
你们为什么在打架?
Why are you fighting?
我们不都是朋友吗?
Aren't we all friends?
看起来我们还有一位观众
Looks like we've still got an audience.
-来前排看戏如何呀?  -石榴
-How about a front-row seat? -Garnet!
你知道嘛  虽然这很扭曲
You know, this is pretty twisted,
但令我受宠若惊的是你喜欢过去那个
but I'm a little flattered that you liked the old me --
无辜  可爱  傻气的我
innocent, loving, stupid.
如果你就好这一口  干嘛不让她一直这样?
If that's your thing, why don't you leave her like this?
离她远一点
Get away from her.
哦  对你真正的朋友你就这么想保护
Oh, you're so protective of your real friends,
对假的朋友你就让她自生自灭
and you're so careless with your fake ones!
-快停下  -那就来阻止我
-Stop it. -Then stop me!
你就是想攻击我  承认吧
You wanna attack me. Just admit it.
要么来实践一下更好?
Or better yet, just try it!
-不  -为什么不
No! Why not?
因为那不是真相
Because that's not the truth!
真相
The truth.
我知道艰苦和困惑的滋味
I've known hardships and confusion,
但爱可以经受住这一切
but love can live through it all,
只要你们一起面对真相
if you face the truth together.
她最后缺少的碎片
Her final piece.
不  停下
No. Stop!
你敢
Don't you dare!
当艰苦的一天过去
♪ When a difficult day goes by ♪
坚持下去很难  但原因正是
♪ Keeping it together is hard, but that's why ♪
你必须尝试  你必须坚持
♪ You've got to try, you've got to try ♪
每当
♪ And when ♪
外面电闪雷鸣
♪ There's a thundering storm outside ♪
在庇护之下  你蜷缩潜藏
♪ Underneath the covers, you huddle and hide ♪
把你的眼睁开  把你的眼睁开
♪ Open your eyes, open your eyes ♪
什--
Wha--
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
被
♪ Stuck ♪
恐惧和羞愧所困
♪ In the middle of fear and shame ♪
每个人都在推卸责任
♪ Everybody's looking for someone to blame ♪
仿佛一场游戏  仿佛一场游戏
♪ Like it's a game, like it's a game ♪
现在我已从输赢中解放
♪ And now I am better than win or lose ♪
我愿选择一个新的方向
♪ There's a new direction that I'd like to choose ♪
其名为真相  其名为真相
♪ It's called the truth, it's called the truth ♪
我们必须要阻止尖晶石
We have to stop Spinel.
等等  你们都有自己的能力
Wait. You guys have your powers.
你们得快去救大家
You've got to go save everybody.
我来对付尖晶石
I'll deal with Spinel.
她会吊打你的  哥们
She'll crush you, dude.
你打不过她的
You can't fight her.
但我还可以和她交涉
But I can still talk to her.
拜托了  抓紧时间
Please, hurry.
好
Right.
开始行动
Move out.
嘿  是你
♪ Hey, you ♪
让我看到那个有解的问题
♪ Show me that solvable problem ♪
我们可以熬过这一切
♪ We can get through this ♪
我愿与你一同
♪ I'll do the hardest part ♪
共渡难关
♪ With you ♪
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
这是真实  这是真实
♪ It's the true, it's the true ♪
这是真实的爱
♪ It's the true kinda love ♪
尖晶石  来吧  让我们好好谈谈
Spinel, come on, we can talk this out.
我不想再玩了
I don't wanna play anymore.
尖晶石  这不是一场游戏
Spinel, this isn't a game!
你知道  我来这里
You know, I came here
是为了在一群陌生人头上发泄我的怒火
to take my anger out on a bunch of strangers,
但我了解你之后
but now that I know you,
我更想要干掉你了
I wanna kill you even more.
我不能理解
I don't get it!
为什么我的能力没有回来  难道我没有重历
Why aren't my powers back? Aren't I reliving
每件发生在我身上的倒霉事吗?
every horrible thing that's ever happened to me?
一个我压根不认识的宝石人要干掉我
A Gem I barely know is trying to kill me.
我得还我妈那些和我一点关系都没有的债
I'm paying for stuff my Mom did that had nothing to do with me.
我还在和我的能力斗争  而世界正走向灭亡
I'm struggling with my powers. The world's about to end!
我到底缺了什么
What piece could I be missing?
这就是我的人生故事
This is the story of my life!
哇  我就知道我会让你受挫
Wow! I knew I was gonna set you back,
但这就是你的故事开端?
but this is how you started?
传奇的史蒂文宇宙?
The legend, Steven Universe?
你一定是逗我呢
You gotta be kidding me.
像你这种没用的废物
How did a powerless loser like you
是怎么成为银河系的救世主的?
become savior of the galaxy?!
我变了
I changed.
这是最后缺失的碎片
That's the final piece.
我从我所有的磨难中学习  所以我成长了
All those struggles, I learned from them, and I grew.
哦天呐
Oh, my gosh.
我忘记的不仅是我的宝石能力
It's not just my gem powers I've forgotten.
对从此幸福生活的执念
All this happily ever after stuff
还让我忘记了我最初获得的能力--
has made me forget the first power I ever had --
改变的力量
the power to change.
我能达成誓言
♪ I can make a promise ♪
我能制定计划
♪ I can make a plan ♪
我能影响他人
♪ I can make a difference ♪
我能坚定立场
♪ I can take a stand ♪
我能努力奋斗
♪ I can make an effort ♪
只要我能够理解
♪ If I only understand ♪
我  我能够改变
♪ That I, I can make a change ♪
听我说  尖晶石
Listen to me, Spinel.
我理解你的感受
I understand.
你经历了这么多
After everything you've been through,
心里一定很痛苦
you must be in a lot of pain.
不  不是的
No. No!
你才不懂
You don't understand.
你不能改变我的感受
You can't change the way I feel!
没错  只有你自己可以
That's right! Only you can.
你能改变一切
♪ You can make it different ♪
你能纠正错误
♪ You can make it right ♪
使它变得更好
♪ You can make it better ♪
我们无需战斗
♪ We don't have to fight ♪
你能努力奋斗
♪ You can make an effort ♪
就从今晚开始
♪ Starting with tonight ♪
因为你
♪ 'Cause you ♪
你能作出改变
♪ You can make a change ♪
一切皆有可能是吧
Just can it, won't ya?!
单凭你唱几首蠢歌是不可能
You can't just make everything better
让事情好转起来的
by singing some stupid song!
你倒是站着说话不腰疼
All that stuff's easy for you to say.
你的改变是往好的方向变
When you change, you change for the better.
我的改变只会越变越糟
When I change, I change for the worse!
我以前只是不够优秀
I used to be just not good enough!
对粉钻来说还不够好
Just not good enough for Pink,
但现在--现在
but now -- now...
我已经没有任何优秀的地方了
I'm not good at all!
很可笑吧?
That's funny, right?
至-至少我对你还是有点娱乐效果的
A-At least you found me entertaining.
你真的有喜欢过我  吧?
You actually liked me, didn't you?
我到底在做什么
What am I doing?
为什么我这么迫切地想伤害你
Why do I wanna hurt you so bad?
我本该是一个好朋友的
I'm supposed to be a friend.
我只想做一个好朋友而已
I just wanna be a friend.
尖晶石
Spinel.
史蒂文
Steven!
不 不 不 不 不  我干了什么好事?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. What did I do?
我毁掉了一切
I've wrecked everything.
行吧  至少也摆脱了你的注射器了
Well, that's one way to get rid of your injector.
那毒药怎么办?这个星球怎么办?
But what about the poison? What about the planet?
你"从此的幸福生活"怎么办?
What about your happily ever after?
世界上不存在永远幸福美满的生活
There's no such thing as happily ever after.
幸福总是需要我努力去维持的
I'll always have more work to do.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
-史蒂文?  -康妮?
-Steven?  -Connie?
史蒂文
Steven!
你在哪
Where are you?
康妮
Connie!
我马上回来  我保证
I'll be right back. Really.
我们看到了大爆炸而且--
We saw that huge explosion and --
我-我没事  没事  你呢?
I-I'm okay. I'm okay. What about you?
我也没事
I'm fine.
狮子
Lion!
你很担心我吧?
Were you worried about me?
当然喽
Sure seems that way.
史蒂文
Steven!
朋友们  爸爸
Guys! Dad!
沙滩市的市民们还好吧?
Is everyone from Beach City okay?
大家都安然无恙而且明白了事情的来龙去脉
Everyone is safe and accounted for.
爸爸 你的手臂
Dad, your arm.
我一时不小心--
Hey, I just got a little careless and --
别担心  马上会恢复如初的
Don't worry. You'll be good as new in no time.
可是史蒂文  你不是失去了--
But, Steven, you don't have your --
史蒂文  你的能力恢复了
Steven! You got your powers back!
这个能力要是能作用于整个地球就好了
It'd be cool if you could do that to the whole planet.
好主意  紫水晶
Amethyst, that's not a bad idea.
哥们  我就随便说说的
Dude, I was joking.
我的天呐  居然真的有用?
Oh, my gosh. That actually worked?
看来我要疯狂啵啵啵了
Looks like I got a lotta kissin' to do.
我们要帮忙吗?
Should we lend him a hand?
我们还是给他递水吧
We should probably get him some water.
亲吻的时候
Staying hydrated is very important
保持嘴唇湿润很重要
when it comes to smooching.
等等  尖晶石
Spinel, wait!
我真的打算回来找你的
I really was going to come back.
我知道
I know.
那你要去-去哪
Then w-where are you going?
我还有事要做
I've got work to do.
获得友谊对我来说并不容易
Friendship isn't going to be easy for me.
我需要付出更多努力
I'm gonna have to work at it.
你鼓舞了我去努力  但...
You make me wanna try, but...
结果太糟了
I've already messed up bad with you.
我希望我可以先试着去认识一个朋友
I wish I could just start from scratch with somebody.
尖晶石  我--
Spinel, I --
在吗史蒂文
Knock, knock, Steven.
是我们呀
It's us.
钻石们
The Diamonds?
我们打扰到你们了吗?
Are we interrupting something?
呃...对
Uh...yeah!
黄钻  蓝钻  白钻  你们来这儿干嘛
Yellow, Blue, White, what are y'all doing here?
是这样的史蒂文  我们在聊天然后--
Well, Steven, we were all talking and --
对不起  但这股臭味是什么?
I'm sorry, but what is that smell?
我没闻到啊
I don't smell anything.
呕  因为你闻习惯了
Ugh. That's 'cause you live here.
是这样 我们在聊天 然后决定--
Anyway, we were talking, and we decided --
不用废话了
This is taking too long!
史蒂文  我们打算来地球
Steven! We've come to Earth
和你一起住
to live with you-u-u!
什么?我的房子可装不下这么多人
What? My house isn't big enough for all of us.
没事  我们可以将就一下  呃...
Oh, well, I'm sure we could make do with, um...
你的星球一直都这么...
Has your planet always been this...
破败吗?
destroyed?
-当然  我们不是在以貌取"球"  -天哪  当然不了
-Not that we're judging. -Goodness, no.
毕竟以貌取人是不对的
Because judging anything based on appearance is wrong!
是吗  我不懂呢
Yeah, I don't know about this.
但  史蒂文  你离开后
But, Steven, it's been so boring
生活太无聊了
since you've left!
我猜我们还是等你
I guess we'll just wait for you
有空再来拜访我们吧
to visit us whenever you're ready.
别这样嘛
Aw, come on. Don't be like that.
只是我正在和别人告别--
I-It's just, I'm right in the middle of saying goodbye to --
你们记得尖晶石吗?
Do you guys remember Spinel?
抱歉  谁来着
I'm sorry, who?
尖晶石  你以前见过钻石们吧?
Spinel, you've met the Diamonds before, right?
对-对  但她们从来没见过我现在这幅样子
Y-Yeah, but they've never seen me like this.
蓝钻  黄钻  白钻  这是尖晶石
Blue, Yellow, White, this is Spinel.
我的钻石--们
My Diamonds.
粉钻的小玩伴?
Pink's little playmate?
是粉钻遗留的宝藏之一
One of Pink's lost treasures.
我妈把她留在太空中的一个悬浮花园里了
Mom left her on a floating garden in space.
你这小可怜
You poor thing.
没事  区区六千年不足挂齿
Aw, it was only 6,000 years.
我倒立着都能做到
I could do that standing on my head!
区区六千年
Only 6,000 years!
真的  不足挂齿
It's true, that's nothing!
还有傻傻的倒立
And that goofy headstand.
我喜欢这个宝石
I like this Gem.
她好可爱  还有粉钻的影子
She's adorable, and so much like Pink.
尖晶石  我--
Spinel, I --
史蒂文  既然你球这么恶心
Steven, since the Earth is so disgusting,
我们只好把尖晶石带回我们的母星了
we'll just take Spinel back to Homeworld with us
你可以留下
and you can stay here.
真的吗?
Really? Huh?
来与我们共住王宫
♪ Come live with us in the palace ♪
这有属于你的房间
♪ There's a room waiting for you ♪
来吧  来吧
♪ Come on ♪ ♪ Come on ♪
来吧
♪ Come on ♪
让我们宠爱你
♪ Just let us adore you ♪
来与我们共住王宫
♪ Come live with us in the palace ♪
这有属于你的房间
♪ There's a room waiting for you ♪
来吧  来吧
♪ Come on ♪ ♪ Come on ♪
来吧
♪ Come on ♪
让我们宠爱你
♪ Just let us adore you ♪
是  我们知道你不是她
♪ Yes, we know that you're not her ♪
但你是她的
♪ But you were hers ♪
你知道爱她是怎样
♪ You know what it meant to love her ♪
而你让我们联想起她
♪ And you remind us so much of her ♪
你觉得你能应付她们吗
You think you could handle them?
她们是真的不太好相处
They're not exactly easy to get along with.
今天  此时
♪ Today, right here ♪
此刻
♪ Right now ♪
我能再爱
♪ I'll love again ♪
我已经找到那人
♪ I've already found someone ♪
让我们宠爱你
♪ Just let us adore you ♪
-今天  此时  -来与我们共住王宫
♪ Today, right here ♪ ♪ Come live with us in the palace ♪
-此刻  我能再爱  -这有属于你的房间
♪ Right now, I'll love again ♪ ♪ There's a room waiting for you ♪
来吧  来吧
♪ Come on ♪ ♪ Come on ♪
-我已经找到那人  -来吧
♪ I've already found someone ♪ ♪ Come on ♪
让我们宠爱你
♪ Just let us adore you ♪
是  我知道你不是她
♪ Yes, I know that you're not her ♪
而我是她的
♪ And I was hers ♪
你们知道爱她是怎样
♪ But you know what it meant to love her ♪
而你们让我联想起她
♪ And you remind me so much of her ♪
今天  此时  此刻
♪ Today, right here, right now ♪
我们能再爱
♪ We'll love again ♪
我们已经找到那人
♪ We've already found someone ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我们来到了未来  一切充满希望
♪ Here we are in the future, and it's bright ♪
没人害怕  没人争斗
♪ Nothing to fear, no one to fight ♪
我无法相信
♪ I can't believe ♪
进步有多大
♪ We've come so far ♪
从此的幸福生活 就在那
♪ Happily ever after, there we were ♪
并就在这
♪ And here we are ♪
快乐地面对着
♪ So happily we'll face ♪
阻拦我们的事
♪ Whatever comes our way ♪
之后  我们可能再次重来
♪ And after, we might do it all again ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
-我们来到了未来  -我每天做好准备
♪ Here we are in the future ♪ ♪ I'll be ready every day ♪
只要我能够说
♪ For as long as I can say ♪
我  我能够改变
♪ I, I can make a change ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我  我能够改变
♪ I, I can make a change ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
我  我能够改变
♪ I, I can make a change ♪
我们来到了未来
♪ Here we are in the future ♪
就在这  就在这
♪ Here we are, here we are ♪
走多远  走多远
♪ Come so far, come so far ♪
充满希望  充满希望  充满希望
♪ And it's bright, and it's bright, and it's bright ♪
我每天做好准备
♪ I'll be ready every day ♪
只要我能够说
♪ For as long as I can say ♪
我已来到了未来
♪ Here I am in the future ♪
-和大家  -我能够改变
♪ With my friends ♪ ♪ I can make a change ♪
因此
♪ That's why ♪
从此的幸福生活  不会变
♪ Happily ever after never ends ♪